{
    "id": "a3a6d7878cf14a71bbe2bf137aee7ef6",
    "title": "Present Perfect Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He ………………….. from the hills.",
            "description": "We make the present perfect tense forms by putting has/have behind the past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "returned",
                "has returned",
                "had returned",
                "have returned"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f6328556d2d64604a64215ab01c66bfd"
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………..…………. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "never helped",
                "have never helped",
                "never help"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d7814617bfa745aeb11401c541aa38c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………….. many books on philosophy.",
            "description": "We use 'has' when the subject is a singular noun or pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "authored",
                "has authored",
                "have authored"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f09cd4257af84b2ea09a848fc534be6c"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………....... a great help to me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "were always",
                "have always been",
                "had always been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cefb4b4c789a469592e65ebeedd96b1b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………… the camera she borrowed from me.",
            "description": "When the subject is a singular noun or pronoun, we use 'has'.",
            "answers": [
                "returned",
                "has returned",
                "have returned"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4a7126df9a94483dbd36a380c0f7eb8d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………............ any interest in politics.",
            "description": "Showed is the past simple form. Shown is the past participle form. We make perfect tense forms with the past participles. ",
            "answers": [
                "never showed",
                "has never shown",
                "has never showed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1a1d65e79a4f40579f773df9c7ae8b2c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Dad ..................... . on the sofa all morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has lain",
                "has laid",
                "has lied"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "afdbeaf89fb14049a24cee03ea5f2c29"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………….. any information about them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not have received",
                "have not received",
                "didn't receive"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b0ad0a9d45b844d48f83864057cf1a36"
        },
        {
            "question": "Your boy ………………….. another window of mine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has broke",
                "has broken",
                "broke"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "75b72f25a5ae413e97774df27c5050f5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. well for the exam.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "prepared",
                "have prepared",
                "has prepared"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "59cc8ce668a646e2af90745a42093532"
        }
    ]
}